# Search parameters for LinkedIn job search
search_parameters:
  job_title: "Backend Developer"
  location: "Remote"
  job_type: "Full-time" # Optional, can be "Full-time", "Part-time", etc.
  experience_level: "Mid-Senior level" # Optional
  easy_apply: true # Only apply to Easy Apply jobs

# Application form answers for LinkedIn
application_answers:
  first_name:
    question: "first name"
    answer: "Sam"

  last_name:
    question: "last name"
    answer: "Clark"

  email_address:
    question: "Email address"
    answer: "samuelclark907@gmail.com"

  country_code:
    question: "Phone country code"
    answer: "United States (+1)"

  phone_number:
    question: "Mobile phone number"
    answer: "2069105322"

  citizenship:
    question: "Are you a US citizen?"
    answer: "Yes"

  sponsorship:
    question: "Do you require sponsorship?"
    answer: "No"

  agree_to_terms:
    question: "Agree to terms"
    answer: true # True for checked, False for unchecked

  disability:
    question: "Do you have a disability?"
    answer: "No"

  java_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Java?"
    answer: "2"

  react_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with React.js?"
    answer: "2"

  understand_contract_role:
    question: "Confirm that you understand this is a Contract position and not a staff permanent role?"
    answer: "Yes"

  aws_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Amazon Web Services (AWS)?"
    answer: "5"

  shopify_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Shopify?"
    answer: "3"

  hydrogen_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Hydrogen?"
    answer: "1" # Or whatever the appropriate answer is

  django_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Django?"
    answer: "3" # Or whatever the appropriate answer is

  python_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Python (Programming Language)?"
    answer: "5" # Or whatever the appropriate answer is

  IaC_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Infrastructure as code (IaC)?"
    answer: "3" # Or whatever the appropriate answer is

  devops_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with DevOps?"
    answer: "3" # Or whatever the appropriate answer is

  linkedin_profile:
    question: "LinkedIn Profile"
    answer: "https://www.linkedin.com/in/samuelclark/"

  website:
    question: "Website"
    answer: "https://samuelclark.dev"

  acknowledge_privacy_policy:
    question: "By clicking 'I acknowledge,' you agree to our Privacy Policy and data processing. Providing accurate information is essential, as any dishonesty may lead to rejection of an application or termination."
    answer: "I acknowledge"

  education_level:
    question: "Have you completed the following level of education: Master's Degree?"
    answer: "No" # Change to "No" if applicable

  background_check:
    question: "Are you willing to undergo a background check, in accordance with local law/regulations?"
    answer: "Yes" # Change to "No" if applicable

  commuting:
    question: "Are you comfortable commuting to this job's location?"
    answer: "Yes" # Change to "No" if applicable

  onsite_setting:
    question: "Are you comfortable working in an onsite setting?"
    answer: "Yes" # Change to "No" if applicable

  containerization_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Containerization?"
    answer: "3"

  orchestration_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with Orchestration?"
    answer: "3"

  cicd_frameworks_experience:
    question: "How many years of work experience do you have with CI/CD frameworks?"
    answer: "3"

  citizenship:
  question: "Our position is funded by a U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) grant, which requires specific citizenship criteria. Are you a U.S. citizen or permanent resident?"
  answer: "Yes"

  full_stack_experience:
    question: "Do you have at least of 5 years of professional experience in full-stack development?"
    answer: "Yes"

  coding_project_video:
  question: "Did you submit a 5-10 min video of your proudest coding project to Dropbox, named as FirstnameLastnameMobile.mp4?"
  answer: "No"

  # Other settings
  settings:
    max_applications: 2 # Max number of applications per session
